Ana Channel applause.
Our guest today is here, hello, this is our farewell exit, please, please, please, please.
Not ha-ha-ha, but there's a lot of things I'm curious about.
I'm not talking about the "ha-ha", I'm talking about a lot of things that I'm interested in. What do you think? This brand-new one.
I was so surprised. We don't have to record on this kind of treatment table,
I don't know anything about it because the recording started the moment I arrived there.
And I ate too late.
No, I'm sorry. I'm sorry about that. I'm sorry.
But it's nice. He also gave me a picture of the "Mere Old Man".
Mm-hmm.
Thank you.
No, no, no, um..,
Can I have one? Listen, big guy.
What is it?
Is it true, Ano, that you like to see things out of order?
Yes, it's true.
Well, that's because, you know, I have very badly aligned wings,
It makes me happy, you know.
But even if Ano-chan is happy, the disapproval of the people watching is great.
I was watching M-1, and I was so happy that I tweeted, "Wow, it's dirty!
When I said, "Wow, it's dirty," in real time, people thought it was a funny comment.
I thought people didn't like it.
If I tweeted that I liked this flower arrangement, it would be totally fine.
That's how people see it when you say "dirty.
I'm sorry... Is "dirty" good?
It doesn't seem human.
It's cute that it looks like it's about to eat gravel.
He swears all the time.
It's a bad word all the time.
Well, I'm glad I like her so much!
I have a bad feeling about today.
Even in show business, Morita san got her teeth fixed
Yeah, yeah, yeah, all the guys fix their teeth
Everyone fixes their teeth, and they say I don't fix my teeth anymore
You don't fix your teeth?
When I'm on M-1 or something
When I'm on M-1 or something, I get a little concerned if I'm forced to do it
Laughing
It's not a laughing matter.
It's not funny at all.
I'm sorry.
I won the competition.
Okay, I'll fix it now.
But Hikaru Ohta, the president of our office, told me not to fix my teeth because there is still a demand for them.
I said, "Well, only here, right?
Anachan TV.
This program is a variety show where Ana-chan tries various things.
Today, though, we have four fun games.
Isn't that a lot?
You mean I'm going to challenge you to a game?
Yes, yes. If the total score arrives somewhere, there will be a gorgeous prize.
Nothing is set in stone.
How many points do you need?
I don't know.
Well, we'll just have to go by the numbers.
You'll give me a grade for doing it right?
Yes, of course.
Yes, please.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
I'll do it, please.
Then I'll do my best.
First of all...
Hagata Rating Check Applause
I don't really feel like applauding.
It's a game of advantage.
I'm going to ask you to eat a certain food and put a dental mold on it.
I'll eat it too, so all you have to do is compare what you chewed and guess your own dental mold.
I think that sounds pretty obvious.
You see, let's start with the easy game.
I feel like I'm going to guess, but oh no, something like that, then please put on a blindfold.
I hate that kind of thing. Oh, God, I hate this show.
We're going to hide it, too. First, I'm going to ask you to take a bite out of an apple.
Okay.
Okay, that's a little scary.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Why?
You don't know what it means.
I'll explain it to him.
Just nibble on it.
I got it.
I was forced to nibble.I was forced to nibble on it.
Is it good?
Tasty is tasty.
It doesn't matter how good it tastes. I'll take a nibble, too.
I can just blindfold myself for now, right?
I should just blindfold myself for now.
Why are you eating so close to me?
I'm scared.
Yum!
It's true, the apples were delicious. It was a nice apple.
Do I mix it?
Yes, yes, yes. Then, please open your eyes.
So, which one of you is from Mr. Iguchi's neat group?
What's with the stickers? Are they affected by my bad fireworks? Will this have any effect?
I'll have to guess.
But B's got more bang for your buck.
There's a gap between the two front teeth.
Between these two front teeth.
This one doesn't have a gap, right?
And there's a gap between my teeth, right?
I don't.
No, because I bit down on it. And there's a gap between my teeth, right? I don't have any.
No, you don't. I bit down on B!
Correct.
Oh, I see.
One point.
Thank you very much.
So now you have a rough idea of what it looks like?
I didn't even want to answer that question for a second.
But let's get right to it. I've known you for many years.
It's because you have a gap in your teeth.
You have a lot of space.
That tells you a lot about yourself.
I certainly felt like this was the first time I'd ever faced it.
to my teeth.
Okay, let's do the second question.
Isn't the blindfold taking too long?
I've been blindfolded for almost the entire time.
And for the next meal, corn on the cob? And, um, can I just say one more thing?
Can you please stop shoving that in my mouth so I can nibble on it?
Okay, I'll take a nibble.
Corn, right?
Did you manage to nibble?
With this? You don't know what you're doing.
I'll nibble too.
I don't get this one.
Okay.
Okay, you can take off the blindfold now.
Oh, okay?
Okay.
Take off the blindfold, please.
I think it's just a matter of... well, b is a little more gouged than b. And a is kind of messed up, but I don't know if that has anything to do with the teeth.
And the a is kind of messed up, but I don't know if that has anything to do with the teeth. It's a bit like a "pi".
Let's put aside the contents.
B is crumpled, right?
I don't know if it's an anaraby or if it was forced into my mouth,
Ana, did you go this far?
It's not the kind of thing a girl would go for in one shot.
I don't know, but I don't think it's the kind of thing a girl would go for in one shot.
Yes, b. The correct answer is: "Don't say the dirty hermaphrodite that Mr. Iguchi ate.
a, yes... a burger... no... zero points... if his teeth are this bad, yes...
I wonder if it has anything to do with the flower day.
I can't get it right...
The second row is still stuck in there... so the teeth are a little weak.
So, if your teeth are misaligned, they're not strong enough?
They're gonna break a little bit.
You're afraid of breaking them?
Aren't you afraid of breaking them?
Yes, I'm afraid.
Of course you are.
I've never bitten into an apple before in my life because I was afraid of breaking it.
What? You're doing a lot today.
So you understand why I'm afraid of breaking it.
I've felt that way about my teeth, too.
I'm afraid of breaking my tooth too... something to hold next to me... something to nurture... something to support me... because I'm not in a group... because I'm not in a group... because I have such an isolated and independent skin... then let's fill in the gaps. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, which gap? Which gap are you talking about?
All these... all these gaps!
Wait a minute, let me reach out.
You don't know what I mean, I mean...
I don't know what you mean, I mean...
You don't have to go that far.
In people's teeth.In people's teeth.
Oh, I'm so happy, I
I mean, I don't get it at all. What's the fun in that?
It's not fun at all.
I'm super happy!
I can't help but notice the gap between your teeth... between the two rows... and on the side, on the side, on the side, on the side... there's not that much to say...
The more you climb up, the bigger it is!
I didn't mean to put it in there.
I didn't mean to put it in, but it's stuck in there... wait, please stop, this is really humiliating... but it's not cute... it's just the guy with the cone stuck in there...
It's not cute, it's just an old man with a cone stuck in his mouth.
Third question.
There's more.
Blindfold me.
Moo!
What's for dinner?
Yes, sir.
Daifuku.
You don't even know what daifuku is anymore.
It won't show any teeth marks.
Especially since it's supposed to show teeth marks.
You mean I can bite off the whole thing.
You can bite off the whole thing.
Is that an A?
No, I don't know.
It's a bun.
Open your eyes, please.
Which one's your teeth, A or B?
Well, what do you think?
The one with the sharp cross section is A.
Well, there's the bean texture, too.
There's a step between them, isn't there?
Yeah, that's right.
I'm a little concerned about the indentation here.
That's right.
I think the A here is an A. No, no, no, it's a B. I think it's a B.
I can do it.
I don't know which one it is.
I don't know... because I found it.
I don't know, it's soft too, so where's the point?
I'm sure it's because it was pushed in...
It's a pity.
I asked Mr. Iguchi about the quiz.
Did you do the questionnaire?
Yes, I did, I did, and I asked 100 people to tell me their top 3 worst answers, and if I got it right, please open the questionnaire.
I don't know how to say this, but what do you mean I wrote it, and I'm doing it, and I'm the respondent?
I'm not sure how I'm supposed to earn points, but it's because satisfaction is worth points, so if this quiz is fun, yes.
I'm not the one who answered the question, I'm the one who answered the question.
I'll give you five chances to answer the question.
I have to guess 3 out of 5 times, right?
I'm the one who has to guess 3 out of 5 times.
Let's go. I asked Westland Iguchi.
What's the trouble with a bad flower arrangement? Please think about it.
Well...
But well, well, well, I really, um, I think I understand.
Okay, okay. You might hit it.
Yes, I might.
I'm so thirsty. That ventilation makes you thirsty.
Okay, so...
What a shame!
What? No?
No, I don't think so.
No, why not?
It's just a question of whether or not your mouth is open.
No, it's not.
Not too close?
Not even close.
If you start with the simplest one, you'll win.
Then, um...
What's so funny?
Please laugh after you say it. Oh, my God.
It's no good, because it's no fun for us.
I understand.
Okay.
I'm going to go.
Um, that's enough.
I'm not talking about the right to an answer, but that's not what this is about.
There's sand in it.
You've got to be kidding me.
I'm not that vacant.
It doesn't matter that much that it's available.Availability doesn't matter that much.
Remember my teeth.
Look closely.
It's a temple.
Enter the shrine.
You'd be mistaken for a man with a ladle.
There's no such thing as water piñata from here.
There's no way! It's not always coming out!
It's full of water.
I get it! When I drink water, water comes out!
Okay? So...
Okay. - Okay.
Around here.
No, it's not! No, it's not, and it's not coming out!
No, no, no, it's simpler than that!
If you keep going like this, you'll never hit anything, because!
What genre? What genre...
Genre...
Is it a way of life? I don't know. It's like a global thing.
Not in the world, but in life?
This one, first and second place is a bit of a comedy...
Comedy? I don't know... comedy... it has a lot to do with my profession...
I'm not sure if it's related to my profession or not.
Shall we go?
I appreciate the teasing, but every time I make a comment, I'm told I'm weird.
You were right again today.
Not quite, but I've got a lot of information.
That's why this is going out today, isn't it?
Is there a comment section or something?
Yes, there is.
Just this one time.
Is there? All the time.
That's why I'm allowed to do shows and stuff.
Yuukunchi, you have fireworks, let's show them to the camera! Let's show it to the camera!
And then they look at me and say I'm weird.
And then it's aired and people say it's weird on Twitter.
A lot of people are concerned about their teeth.
When was the first time you noticed that your teeth were not smoothing?
When was the first time you noticed that your teeth were not so good? Fireworks, of course, are bad everywhere you look, but maybe that's just because we were in the country.
When I went to the dentist in town, he would usually tell me that I should straighten my teeth.
But when I go to the dentist in town, he usually says, "You should straighten your teeth. Because they can't.
It's more like a test of my skill, or if they say, yes, then try it, because I can't do it.
It's like Pandora's box.
Surprisingly, nobody told me.
Well, it's just that during the four-day checkup, that school...
Like C-2.
C-2, B-1.
That's when I first heard about it.
I don't know...
I don't know which group it is.
But I'm glad I didn't get it fixed.
Until the first year of the new year.
Well, I don't know which group it is, but I'm glad I don't have to fix it. Until the first year of the year.
Well, well, I don't know. I don't know which it is.
I'm glad I didn't have to fix it until the first year of the new year.
I'll have to take that into consideration.
Third place is really super simple.
So, I get it.
It's hard to eat food.
No, it's not.
No? No?
After you eat it.
I can't taste it after I eat it.
That has nothing to do with your teeth! It's a tongue thing.
I can't taste what I've eaten.
Yes, I can!
I can't feel my teeth.
Yes! It's not your teeth or anything.
How many more times do I have to answer this!
I've already answered five times, and that was a long time ago.
It's true.
[ED]
I'm a...